[
Music] That's it
friends, welcome to the Option Gyan channel
friends, as you all
know that the market is a lifetime trend, so
I have already discussed with you guys that in
such a situation, we will not invest our entire capital here,
that friends, the
market is a lifetime trend, but whether there is a correction or not,
normally also friends, until there is
a correction in the market, I should never
invest my entire capital,
we should destroy 50% of our capital,
we should always give 50% of our capital,
you should keep that money in liquid funds
and whenever there is a correction in the market,
you people should
not spend it on good stocks at that time, but you should
always keep investing,
friends, that is why I give you
guys a delink torque, I
give you a Delhi juice torque, friends, the
reason for this is that if anyone is
adding a member with me, then from that day onwards, he has some
stock to like
and I will definitely tell you guys where to edit that thing,
where to invest it.  So,
you guys should
strictly follow that thing, my stop loss
friends, sometimes it is quite far but
that stop loss friends, I do not give such that
20 percent, those are stars,
friends, I have placed them on some support or the other,
if that support breaks
then the chart goes negative, otherwise otherwise it means
that the stock bounces back, so if
you go there and wish, then
basically you will see a loss for a while,
but if you just do it now, you will
see a very good profit in a few days,
hello friends, you guys have to back inside this red top,
only you guys should share four or
five stop losses and do
not put all the money in that stock, where I
ask you to wish, you guys should go there and do it
and like these two, the market is
quite good, so whenever you get ten to fifteen percent,
you guys should book your profit
and
otherwise you guys have to
always keep in mind to wish, are you
ready to unite, taking stop loss is not a wrong thing,
friends, it is a very good habit, today
I am  I have brought this topic friends,
its name is Sabrose, it is an
auto sector share, friends, this
small cap pack small cap share friends, friends, you do
n't know when it increases by 20 to 30 percent
and you don't even know when such 20 percent are cut,
so you people have to buy this stock at the
current rate i.e. around 30
and around 30 you only have to
invest 30 percent capital, friends, the
rest of you,
I will modify it a little,
you people should invest 50% of the capital here, that is, if it is
in Twenty-20, then you people should invest 50% of the capital
here, that is around 30
and the remaining 50% that you have to invest,
that is around 245, at that time
around 2.5, you have to see that if the stock is
not able to achieve the 2 to front part upwards for two-three days, it
consolidates below 245 for four days, then you people will
close your position, this is for those people
who have a position, if you
hold the stock in the long term, then its fundamental  It
is quite strong, so now you
can get good benefits, but for that you will have to be
patient. Money is made through friends in the market.
I discuss its fundamentals with people.
Friends, this is the Rodhaak app. If
you click on this topic, it takes you to the
fundamentals. This window
opens, click on fundamentals.
After that, click on details here. It takes you to the
ticket.
Here we check its fundamentals. There is a
separate investment chakli. Out of five,
two are looking positive. Only the dividend
point is negative. But friends,
after that, if the fundamentals of the company are
strong, I will show you the logic behind it. So,
look at the financial times of the company,
friends, when you will see it increasing,
you will see a
small box kept in 120, its
revision, you know that it is 2019 and Lokdhun, in
201 you will see a little further on the shop.
But these six months are giving problems
and the only profit that is visible is for only
6 months, so right now the chairman has told the company that if the
company does well then
both the revenue and profit of the company will increase,
if we talk about the financial statement then
you can see all the three
points surrounded in the financial statement which is quite
good,
friends the
net income version of the company is increased a lot
through industry, if
you can see the industry margin friends, at the same time the
net interest margin of the company is
looking positive, it is 50%, so I wanted to
tell you that the
fundamentals of the company are very strong, despite this
friends,
I am also sharing with you
that in every quarter friends mutual fund
scams are taking away their wealth,
see that people are
investing in mutual funds which are looking patent, due to which the
fundamentals of the company are very
strong and you are getting it near 210, then
definitely buy this stock  You
should consider both long-term and position wise
friends, I hope
you liked my video
and it will be very beneficial for you all,
with this hope friends I end my video,
thank you
friends, if you like this video then
please do not forget to like, share and subscribe,
thank you for watching my video
[Music]